DAVE WOLFBERG

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Full Stack Software Developer with experience building a diverse set of frontend and backend projects. Lifelong learner with a growth mindset who is excited to contribute to impactful projects. Patient puzzle solver with the ability to stay calm and collected in high pressure situations and drive to deliver the highest quality work under stringent time restrictions. Charismatic communicator and highly collaborative professional who has spent a decade on the road as a touring musician developing grit, flexibility, and a strong team ethic.

WORK HISTORY

Freelance Software Developer, 03/2022 - Current

Self-Employed, Remote

- Facilitated clients visions for Wordpress sites allowing them to edit their own custom websites.
- Installed cyber security protocols to protect Wordpress domains from cyber attacks.
- Created custom themes based on needs of business.

Software Engineering Fellow, 12/2021 - 03/2022

General Assembly, Remote

- Created interactive touchscreen Pedalboard Builder App for musicians with MERN stack, AWS S3, and React-Beautiful Drag-n-Drop.
- Built "Make-Your-Own-Burger-App" using Express, and MongoDB that allows user to create burgers and view their creations.
- Collaborated with team of 2 others to make "Smart Cocktail Recommendation App" utilizing Django, Python, PostgreSQL, and Materialize.
- Learned essential fundamental skills in web development, computer science and database engineering principles.

Guitarist - Touring/Session Musician, 05/2013 - 11/2021

Shallou, Zero9:36, Overstreet, And Many Others.

- Worked on tours, recordings and film orchestrations.
- Actively managed social media presence providing content for sponsorships and endorsements.
- Repaired and maintained quality of various instruments.
- Provided musical background for live shows such as ballets, operas, musical theatre and cabarets.
- Managed projects with dance departments creating scores and choreography.

EDUCATION

Certificate, Software Engineering Immersive, 03/2022

General Assembly - Remote

- Cos Angeles, CA 90068
- (201) 615-4663
- Dave.M.Wolfberg@gmail.com

SKILLS

- HTML, CSS, Javascript, Python, Ruby, PHP, SQL.
- React, Express, Node, Django, Ruby on Rails, Wordpress.
- Bootstrap, Materialize.
- PostgreSQL, MongoDB.
- Docker, Mocha, AWS.
- Trello, Lucid Chart, Creating ERDs, Wireframes, and Pitch decks.
- Zoom, Slack, Github.
- Expansive knowledge of music, art and social media trends.

WEBSITE, PORTFOLIO, PROFILES

- https://github.com/Wolfcodes91/
- http://portfoliodave-wolfberg.herokuapp.com/
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/davewolfberg/

CERTIFICATIONS

Mimo - Certificate of Achievement in Python (May '22)

Mimo - Certificate of Achievement in SQL (May '22)

Mimo - Certificate of Achievement in Frontend Development (May '22) Berklee College of Music - Boston, MA